I mean, what-what
am I supposed to do?
(Penny:)Uh, keep your mouth
off other women.
(Leonard:)I can do that.
Uh, uh, f-from now on,
(Leonard:)this mouth--
you and food, that's it.
(sighs)
(Penny:)Okay.
(Leonard:)Yeah?
(Penny:)Look, I'm not happy
this happened,
(Penny:)but I think
I can get past it.
(Penny:)I mean, we weren't
engaged at the time,
(Penny:)and it was just kissing.
(Sheldon:)Right.
(Leonard:)Just kissing.
(Leonard:)It wasn't even very good.
(Leonard:)She was a smoker.
I'd just been seasick...
(Penny:)Okay, that's enough.
Stop talking.
(Stuart:)So...
(Leonard:)we're still
getting married?
(Sheldon:)Yes.
(Leonard:)Because we love each other.
(Leonard:)And it's the happiest day
of our lives.
(short laugh)
Don't push it.